For me, 20, 000 is a lot of money.
But to get, I remember all the guys made
a hundred thousand dollars, probably all
my free time when I'm not at the gym or
playing tennis or stay with my girlfriend.
It's for a big bounty.
Yeah.
So still today, a lot of SQL
injections on, on accurate one.
So a lot of.
Problems with all, with WAF 2, I was
able to bypass some WAFs and some cases.
My automation is only for recon,
not to exploit anything, because
probably, uh, the exploit thing
with nuclear or something, there are
guys doing this more fast than me.
so much for joining me
for the podcast this time.
Uh, for the viewers who don't
know you yet, can you please
introduce yourself a little bit
and tell us about your background?
Okay.
So thank you again for inviting me.
I'm really excited about this
pod questions and the question.
So yeah.
So about my background, So
I'm a book hunter and pen
test on Hacker one with four.
I think I have four or five years on
Hacker one I, and, and after that,
uh, I, I work, I work uh, as uh,
cybersecurity tech lead, uh, uh,
cybersecurity constitute in Brazil.
And I'm pen test leader in Hacker one two.
So I work with both and, uh, this is me.
I think and I was invited, um,
five times to live hack events and
hacker one and I really like it,
send a lot of bugs on boot bounty.
Yeah.
So are you not the full time
backbone hunter now?
Yeah, not, not.
Have you considered it?
Yeah.
Um, I think maybe it's a possibility
to me because probably my income
from boot bounty, it's pretty low.
It's really, it's more than I receive
from my, my work, really more, but I
really like at work at, uh, this Brazilian
cybersecurity, it's, it's good work there.
I have some friends and I really,
I really like at work there.
So it's, it's, it's a good job.
I can do really good things there.
The vulnerability, uh, I
showed to you was there.
Using the, the serial kilobyte
pass, get, get his collection.
So I have good opportunities.
That's to test Brazilian
Brazilian companies.
So, yeah, I like work there.
Yeah, that's, I think that's, that's
the common theme among all of the
back hunters that we like like bounty.
But also being alone is
a little bit problematic.
Yes.
Yeah,
you are really true.
Very impressive That's
still only work part time.
You've got to almost 22,
000 reputation on HackerOne.
Yeah
So I I'm very excited to
to speak with you.
Awesome.
I probably owe my friends Free
time when I'm not at the gym or
playing tennis or stay with my
girlfriend, it's for a big bounty.
Yeah.
So yeah, all my free time is for a
big bounty and probably maybe this is
the reason why I have this reputation.
Well done one way or another.
So Uh, are you more of a
automation based hunter?
Are you a manual hunter?
Are you something, something in between?
So, uh, yeah, maybe I'm in between
these juice, the, these two options
because I have automation, but
only to, my automation is only
for Rico not to exploit anything.
Yeah, because probably, uh, the,
the exploit thing with nuclear or
something, there is more, there are,
there are guys doing these more fast.
Yeah.
It's a race.
So it looked like a race.
So I didn't, it's like this, this.
So probably my, my, my
automation is only for recon.
What I have, it's, I have a huge,
my SQL database, it's all my,
yeah, with all my, all my, yeah.
My scope from bookbug programs
and all, all the time my script
is running and do the record.
And if I have some updates for hacker
one, uh, uh, these updates notify me and
I have the assets on my, my telegram chat.
So I received that and
maybe this is a good target.
Oh, maybe this program, uh, this
program has now with the car
scope so I can look there and yes.
So my, my automation, it's only for
recon and receive the updates from the
programs and my, but my, my hunting,
it's only manual testing, looking
at application and that's things.
Yeah.
How, how technically do you have connected
hacker one updates to a telegram chat?
So, uh,
maybe in, uh, at the first time was.
Really hard because we need we need
to your scripts need to be hitting
the hacker on API a lot of times
to to get the updates in the time.
But I think it's OK now because because
I I I'm writing the script a lot of time.
So maybe the script is stable.
Now and I did have so problems,
but maybe at first time I had a lot
of a lot of books and description.
Not the script is not working
well and I have losing scope.
An example.
Some I remember to see some time.
My script is not looking all the
scope is only looking the first page.
Not all the scope.
So I fixed them, uh, making a for loop,
uh, uh, looking all the pages of this
scope from API, because I didn't know
the API only show a page of scope, not
all the scope is some progress that the
huge scopes with a lot of domains and
these, and probably I was missing that.
So this, this is what, uh, This is
one of the mistakes I have in the,
in the way, but I think probably
now it's more stable, but, but my
automation is only for HackerOne.
Yeah.
Because probably implementing other
APIs or others, uh, platforms will
be more, I will be more work that.
Yeah.
And
it's always when you write something,
it's like, it's a, it's a cool idea and
you think it's going to be quick and then
it takes time and more time and bugs.
Yeah.
A lot of
bugs.
Sometimes I. I didn't receive the
notifications on Telegram and I think, oh,
probably there is something not working
well, I need to check on the server.
Yeah.
What other alerts do you have?
For some, I don't know, do you
monitor JavaScript, for example?
No, I didn't monitor any JavaScript.
Uh, but what I, what I monitor with,
with this, with my automation is,
uh, every, every day I do the recon.
And.
I have the responses for the same domain
in, in a time and in, uh, an example.
I run the record yesterday, today,
and there are going to be tomorrow.
I have all the HTTPS, uh, Parameters
in the MySQL database and I can
compare if an example, if the
status code yesterday was 401
and today was 200 and
yesterday will be 200.
So I historical in my, in my automation.
So you store the HTTPS parameters.
So there's like the status
code, number of words, number
of lines, something like this.
Yeah,
you don't actually,
you don't actually, Oh, yeah,
because, because, um, HTTPS,
uh, has a, uh, a parameter.
You can get the hash of the
body so you can, I did it.
I have these, but I need to
work to improve maybe the
way to view these things.
But I was capable, uh, if I search
some, some domain example from a book
balance program, I was capable to see
if the page was changing in the time.
If the, the hash gen bo
I think it's gen body.
Yeah.
The name of the hash.
If, if this has changed, probably
the application changed and probably
the application will, probably
the application was update or
something, or have the body change.
Yeah, that's very interesting.
Yeah.
Doesn't
it cause too
many false positives
because the hash is very,
very strict.
Yeah.
We have a lot of many false
positives, but sometimes I have
good, I have good, good examples.
So I will show an example to you.
I really like PHP page because.
When you saw PHP, probably we
will find some books there.
So I was monitoring this page and for
this page, the page was the same, the same
hash, same hash, same hash, same hash.
And someday I will look
and the hash change.
Oh, probably is there an update here.
And I was capable to find a
new endpoint and access there.
So it's, it's fine because if
you look for the right, The right
domains, the rights of domains,
you can find good things there.
Yeah, but it's hard to, to, to
limit this because do you have like
just, um, you monitor this just
for the main page, like the slash?
No, it's only the main
page.
Only the main page?
Yeah, the main page.
Because, uh, probably, uh, all the
page will be more complex to do.
And yeah.
I don't know, maybe my SQL is
not the best database to do that.
Because imagine we store all these things.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
Like sometimes when I think of
writing something like this, I want
to, well, first of all, I don't
want to spend all the time on the
development, but I can accept it.
But then I want to, Uh, somehow
limit the amount of noise.
Yeah.
To, to actually, so it gives me leads,
but doesn't give me everything every day.
Yeah.
So it's a very nice balance that
you, that you seem to have, I think
probably in my automations, uh, what
I really, really use is this, this
scope update because it's, it's fun.
This, it's really cool
because, um, uh, sometimes.
The program update the scope, but
didn't send emails to other people's
or, or the subscribe didn't work well.
So this functionality to update
scope, it's really awesome because
give me the visibility of all the
scope updates from the programs.
I didn't have that because my,
my, my telegram chat has a lot of
messages all the day because all these
problems that update changing as yeah.
As more things, I will show
an example to you here.
So today I have 10 a.
m. Yesterday, yesterday.
So yeah, a lot of updates
from these programs.
Yeah, even
in the beginning when you said it, I
imagined that, uh, the way I thought
it may be done is you have some
webhook on the email mail hook, but
now you realize, okay, there's not
always an email sent no scope update.
Not just now.
I realize this.
Yeah.
So what I do really is get all the
time the scope from HackerOne and after
that compare it with my scope in my SQL
database and comparing that, oh, there
is some new here, send to Telegram and
start storing in Yeah, that's very smart.
Yeah.
And do you, every day, do you hunt like
on whatever your automation shows you?
Yeah, when, when I have good targets,
an example, I saw that, uh, I saw
maybe here there's some good things.
What I was thinking to do to improve my
automation is, uh, use HTTPS in these
new domains to check the technologies.
Because if I have some good technology
like PHP or something, probably this is
really good and I can, maybe it's good.
Take some, some, take some time here
because probably will be good stuff here.
Yeah,
yeah, that's cool.
You make, you motivate me to start
doing something similar as well.
Yeah, I have some kind of, I have some
JavaScript monitoring which I use and, but
I use it on programs I don't even handle
anymore and I get updates every few days.
And I never actually like
created the automation.
The automation where I would
really stick to it and I would
actually use it properly.
Yeah.
But I think it's, I think
it's incre incredibly useful.
So I have to,
yeah, the texts from the
updates were, it's useful.
I really use that.
Yeah.
That's really awesome.
Yeah, that's very, that's very smart.
And that's weird.
There's no native functionalities do it.
Not just now I realize.
Yeah.
So, uh, I, I was talking with Omi.
I dunno.
I, I'm.
Talking about years, love me in the past,
we're talking about maybe it's better
for hacker one API if they use webhooks
to send to us, because imagine all all
the day my script is honey and it's
running and hit the hacker one API, get
all the programs and do this every, Okay.
Minutes.
Do, do, do, do.
So maybe, maybe this, uh, uh,
maybe this consume a lot of
resource on HackerOne API.
So maybe Webhooks can finish with
this, this, consume enough resources.
That would be easy.
And also not only on the HackerOne API,
but then you have to pull it yourself.
You have to diff it yourself.
Yeah.
So it's, it's a lot of code.
It's a lot of resources and
the Webhook would be easier.
Yeah.
Although for bug bounty, the
thing is, if something is hard,
it's, it is the reason Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's true.
Okay.
So you have the automation.
You, you start handing on some new
domain that automation gave you.
What's, where do you start?
What do you hack?
A lot of fuzzing.
Probably.
I really like to do fuzzing.
Yeah.
I really like to use way more.
And these, these tools would give me the
historical things from this, this domain.
So fuzzing.
Historic, uh, historic things for this.
I might use way more or
other, other, others tools.
So I really like, uh, I really like to
search on Google being that the goal and
others search to, I really like site, uh,
two points, I think two points, two points
are not two dots, uh, colon, colon, colon.
I think, yeah, a site
column and, uh, domain.
com.
So you, uh, it's, it's really
awesome because when you do that, a
lot of these, these searching genes
give you a lot of good end points.
Uh, so I really do that way more in a
lot of fuzzing and fuzzing over fuzzing.
In example, you find a new path.
Oh, probably I need to do f more here.
I, I need, I need to do rec recursive f
because sometimes this can be, uh, can
be a problem to the customer because
you, maybe you can turn, turn it all
or off or maybe, uh, stop the server.
This, this is normal, so you
need to, uh, for me, uh, the
normal, now it's use low threads.
Big word, least fuzzing out the past
looks for for good things and after
fight a bad fuzzy and again and again.
And look what's back classes do fast for.
I really like access.
Yes, improper access control.
Insecure sterilization, sickle injection.
I have a lot of For me.
So you have like a one large
word list with everything?
Yeah.
What, what I can, what I can see
on the application, probably I will
test an example, uh, a few months
ago I, I saw in pdf f reader, in
this PDF reader, I was capable to.
Attach files.
I don't know if you saw this
kind of vulnerabilities and I
was able to local file inclusion.
So yeah, maybe probably for me when I
found an application, I try, I try to
test all these things on the application.
XSS, misconfiguration, information
disclosure, SQL injection,
XSXXE.
So all these things I try.
Application and if I have
some specifications and
with, and this PF reader.
So this is interesting and I test all,
I I want to test this, uh, uh, SSRF on
this PDF reader, LFE on this PF reader.
So what I, I, everything I, I, I,
I can le see on the application.
I try, I really like it
to the Hack Tricks book.
I don't know if you know this.
Yeah, of course.
This domain, this is really, really good.
Didn't it disappear recently?
Yeah, I don't know because the, the,
the URL, the domain is working, but
the Google is not showing anymore.
I don't know why.
Okay.
Interesting.
I don't know why.
Maybe.
I don't know, but the Google
is not, is not showing anymore.
But if you have the, the URL, the
URL of Hacktrix, it's working.
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't know what's happened.
Yeah, so your, your word list, how
many, how many positions does it have?
Oh, probably, I have, I have
some huge, uh, word lists.
The one that you use, just you open
an endpoint parameters by default?
Uh, no, uh, the, the word list to
fuzzing a path in a web application
probably wants to meet an entry.
Okay.
And to fuzzing parameters, maybe, Uh, 300,
I think, entries to fuzzing parameters.
An example, I have an endpoint, I, I
try to see if it gets, um, if in this
endpoint there is some get parameter
interesting and I, I fuzzing again.
I really like it.
XH, these two, two fuzzing
parameters is really nice.
I don't know if you know this.
No, I don't.
It's really nice because, uh, for me, the
param, parameter is, it's really slow.
I don't know because I didn't have
good experience with parameter.
So these two, do you mean paraminder?
Sorry, my English is very good.
So I really like in my burp
suite, my setup, I have another
extension called ascend 2.
Yeah.
And I use it This extension
to pipe the request.
Just these tools like XH, XSQL
map and other custom tools.
I have an example.
I have a custom tool to
say as far as application.
So I pipe the request to these
tools and it's really good
work with that.
Yeah, but do you fast?
You said there is a word is of how big?
My, my main words list.
Yeah.
An example.
I have the normal words list.
Yeah.
If, if I use the normal, the normal
words list and the words list didn't
work, uh, probably, uh, this words
list has one or two millions entries.
And you always fast with
one or two million entries.
No, no.
Probably give a few days working.
So yeah, I do a lot.
And waiting, do my, do my
work and stay where it is.
So you just leave it in
the background, don't you?
Yeah, sometimes, yeah, sometimes I'm
looking, but I'm afraid to, to, how
can I say, I'm afraid to turn off,
it's not turning off the servers of the
customers, but I'm really afraid of that.
So, uh, what I do is look
the polish of the problem.
If, if the problem allow, you can only do.
20 racks per second.
I, I, I use these metrics
to, to configure the fuzzy.
Okay.
So, yeah.
Interesting.
Yeah.
I, I, I know I'm, but it's fuzzing,
but, but I had no idea, like Someone
fathers with such a large world list.
Yeah.
I think he, I'm a, I'm, I'm patient.
So I get, yeah, I start the fluffy,
putting another monitor and see
working what I'm due to working.
Sometimes I minimize and look there.
Because sometimes you, sometimes, uh,
the, the, the program has a policy, you
are in the policy, but the application
down and you need to turn off.
Yes, and stop.
You are, you are right because you are
in the policy, but the application is
not, uh, good enough to, to, is not
capable to deal with, with that request.
So I stopped and didn't test, didn't
do fuzz in there anymore because
probably the application will be down
and a lot of problems will be happen.
Yeah, yeah.
So this is for fuzzing the paths.
Uh, so then how do you fuzz parameters?
Do you also use a big word list
to fuzz all the parameters?
I
really like to use a tool called GAP.
I don't know if you know this tool.
I really like the dev
from these extensions.
I use it way more from this guy to get.
More information about to recon and
these extensions really good gap
burp extension because with that
extension, you can use your burp story,
uh, an example, all your navigation
story with all the path and points,
parameter and the response containing
parameters, uh, containing points.
You can use the extension to get all
these things and generate wordless.
This is very nice.
Yeah.
So sometimes when I'm spending a
lot of time in some programs, I use
that word release to add to my word
deletion and do fuzzing with that.
So yeah, the result with this case
is, with this case and this extension
and way more are really good.
Yeah.
Can you send this to me so I can put
it in the description for the viewers?
Sure, sure, sure.
Really, uh, let me send this and
another, I really like this way more.
Yeah, way more.
Very good as well.
It's really, really good.
I really like the tools from this guy.
I give a lot of, because
his guy has, uh, Coffee.
Yeah.
Uh, oh, yeah.
Buy me a coffee.
I do a lot of coffee.
Yeah, I give a lot of coffee to this guy
because the tools are really, really good.
That's very nice to get to give back to
the tool creators.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's awesome.
So, um, when you fast these parameters,
do you fast for all back classes at once?
Yeah, I really like to
use Burpee Bounty Pro.
I don't know if you know, some
people don't, don't, some people
don't like this, this Burpee Bounty.
I like because the, the tests of Burpee
Bounty are more Because, an example,
the Burp Suite Scanner, it's, I have the
feeling it's huge and do a lot of things.
I really like the Burp Bounty because
you can create custom templates
and you can create custom rules.
And the rules there and the templates
there are really, are really nice.
So, I use a lot.
Uh, this template when I have
the parameters to, to find if I
have some SQL injection or XSS.
Yeah.
But I really like to use BuffProf.
But sometimes I use the BuffScanner.
It's not the best option because the
scanner for me, it's really heavy.
Yeah.
So, but sometimes I use them too.
You seem to, to rely a lot on
burp and different extensions.
Yeah.
I, I have a lot of extinctions and Yeah.
I really like to automate my process
to hunting, to be, to, to, how can I
say, to have to, to easier my life.
Yeah.
To be efficient.
To be, yeah.
And example with xh in the past when,
when I didn't know send to you, I will
send the linking to send it to you.
To you too.
Oops.
Because, uh, in the past.
I copy the request, saving
a file, run the command.
So this is really, uh, really slow,
but with this, this extension sent
to you and the comment pipe, you
can send it to a Mac terminal and
sent to X eight sent to SQL map.
So yeah, it's really, for
me, it's really productive.
Yeah.
I use Piper for the similar thing.
So Piper, have you, are
you familiar with it?
Yeah.
I think Piper do the
same has sent to, right.
Okay.
Yeah.
A few options as well.
Oh, it has, uh, sometimes you can also
have like Inside the verb, you can like
have commentators or, uh, which means
for each request that matches particular,
uh, criteria, you run some command and
then the output of this command is in
the comment of the request in verb.
You can also have the message viewer.
So when you have like pretty,
raw, uh, I don't know, GraphQL
hex view in the request.
You can also have some
output of a command.
And you can also just do,
do, do what you say, send it.
And it's very efficient when, yeah,
it's when something just automatically
gets run in the background.
It's so nice because you don't
have this time, copy, paste.
Yeah, you do what you need to do and
the things are working automatically.
So, yeah, yeah, it's awesome.
I need to test Piper.
I think I remember today.
I don't know, I didn't remember who
was, who was it, but it's very powerful.
It's very open
and you can do so many things with it.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm, I'm using, uh,
send to you because I, I
remember to see the extension.
Yo, this is, this is awesome.
I need to use that.
And now it's.
It's the normal to me is use that.
Yeah.
What other extensions do you use?
Uh, let me check here.
I have a lot of, this is my, my work.
I really like this extension.
W X D L E R this extension.
I don't know if he,
Oh, the, I dunno how, how to . It's WSDL
is is some type of format, isn't it?
Yeah.
It looks like, looks like an API format.
Yeah, and you can, and you can send
the, uh, the, the WSDL to the extension
and they will give the request to
you and for create the request and
you can only send to B two test.
Yeah.
Because some.
Some XML, uh, API are really
hard to create the request.
It's more difficult than
Swagger, for example.
So I really like this extension.
I really like the Flow extension.
I don't know why, but I really like this
extension because What does Flow do?
I'm not familiar.
Flow is the same as Let me, let
me open a new BURP suite here.
I really like Flow because it's, uh,
there is Logger but I didn't, um, I'm
not familiar with Logger So I use Flow
to get the request for an extension.
So, an example, I really
like the extension Reflector.
This extension is really
good to get some XSS.
So, but sometimes he
doing a lot of requests.
I didn't know what is happen
and with flow extension, I can
solve the extension requests.
So I really like it.
Flow.
This is, this is why I like it.
Yeah.
So an example of gap as shows to you.
With all this really good
in what we can do there.
The BuffBot Pro, I have the
license, I paid for the license.
They support Eduardo, I think
Eduardo is a great guy too.
Create this, this rate too.
Uh, I really like this extension, burp.
js like Finder.
Because when you are, I don't
know if you know this extension.
Uh,
link finder, yes.
But yeah, but the one in burp, is
it some kind of wrapper around it?
Uh, uh.
I don't know.
Does it call link finder CLI to
under the hood or is it something you
let me?
Yeah.
JS link finder.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's, it's really cool because
you are, uh, testing the web
page and loading other page.
And this extension, it's using
rejects to get some endpoints and
some good stuff from the GS file.
So it's really, it's really awesome.
Use the extension.
Um, I sent to you reflect or gap.
Yeah.
The Hubbard Bouncing Flow, the
Digitalization Scanner, I use a lot.
Login Plus Plus, I use because it's
necessary on a HackerOne paint testing.
Because you need to have, you need
to auto save your paint, your log.
Because it's important to
have it installed this.
Okay.
Because of the testing.
And this guy works.
One or two times with me.
So I have this extinction too, to test
It maybe sometimes work,
maybe sometimes not.
It's curious because, uh, my first bug
was with this extinction different.
It was, uh, uh, it was a remote code
execution, but it was fun because
it's a program with a large scope,
and I use this extension in the.
The main page, because the
main page are a blank page.
When I use this extension,
you see the headers here.
Which extension are we talking about?
Uh, sorry?
Which extension?
403 Bypasser?
Yeah,
403 Bypasser.
So, it worked only one time, but this time
we're so happy I have the extension here.
Because with this specified header, I
was capable to access the application.
The application, before the
application was only a white box.
page with this header.
I was capable to assess the
application and all the application
with the CV for remote code.
Yeah.
So, so I have the extension too.
That's cool.
Yeah.
It's a lot.
You seem to have like your, some
people, for example, um, the
last, the last podcast that was
published was with, uh, RemyPack.
He seems to have like his center
of hacking in the browser.
He has like JavaScript bookmarklets
and trying to be able to do
everything from the browser.
And you on the other hand, you have
like your verb, all the extensions too.
So this is like your
center of, of hacking.
Yeah.
But I, but I really like hacking in
Google Chrome because of an example,
I have this Chrome for my, my
personal stuff and this Chrome better
Chrome to only use it with work.
And there I, I, I really like this
version because, um, I really like
using work to hack because the
developers too are really good.
Uh, I really like the, these options
because sometimes, uh, when you have some.
Uh, apps.
You can debug the app using the dev
tools and you can override the books.
The burp says, give this name overriding
can change the GS and changing there.
You have different response in the,
in the single page application.
And with that, sometimes you can bypass.
Out in the front end out and assess
all the application and understand how
the API is used by the application.
So yeah, I use a lot.
How
about browser extensions?
Do you also have as many browser
extensions as crow as burp extensions?
Oh, let me.
So I didn't have a lot browser extension.
I have this extension because it's good.
What's the name?
gitch.
It's only to find.
Uh, when you have Oh slash gee
slash Yeah, because sometimes I, I,
I, I just use nuclei a lot because
nuclei probably will show that.
Yeah.
So this is a, a really good, you
can find some good stuff here to
get so cold and tokens and something
when you, when you have a, a look
at a look at dot, gee, I use this
extinction for my blind and success.
Yeah.
This is a really good extension.
I dunno if you know that.
No.
What's the name?
I, I have all my.
Pay blind.
She says payloads here.
I didn't know the name and
it's out blind access manager.
Okay.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Because I have my blind XSS payloads here.
My domain gives you in the history with
the page and where I use the payload.
Oh, that's very nice.
Yeah.
It's really good because when you
saw the blind, she says, yes, you
didn't know where you are sending.
So this extension really good
to, to manage my blind XSS.
Yes.
For blind XSS, what do you use as the, I
use,
I
think, uh, let me see.
Is it XSS Hunter?
Yeah.
XSS Hunter.
Let me see, self hosted.
I only self hosted this.
Let me see if he's, yeah, this guy,
the pre cut ad, but I use this guy.
It's really good.
I didn't have any problem.
The only problem I have with this guy was
sometimes, uh, the webpage are so huge,
so huge, and when the, the request are
trying to upload the, the, the screenshot
to the server, we have this problem.
So I need to change the no
js limit size for the final.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe, maybe I lose some, I lose in
the past some, some byte access for that.
I don't know.
I didn't remember if
So travel security, uh, took
over, bought this extension.
So now they, I think they maintain
it now because I think the original
maintainer sort of stopped supporting it.
Oh, okay.
So this is the, the new extension.
Yeah, yeah, but it's still the,
the version that's hosted by
them is a little bit limited.
Okay.
So if you want to have full
functionality, you have to self host it.
Okay.
Maybe I use this express.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I use that.
I use that because I remember.
I think it's
the same.
Yeah.
I remember because there
is this Docker config.
Yeah.
I remember to, to.
Okay.
Yeah.
I remember to change here and
because I changed from, uh,
email to discord notification.
There is a, there is a pull request here.
Uh, change here at these
discord and Slack integration.
Yeah.
So this guy made this all the work for me.
So yeah, thank you.
Adam G yesterday.
Yeah, very nice.
Yeah.
You're amazing in terms
of how many tools you use.
You like, especially that now
I'm now in the moment where I
feel always, I don't fuzz enough.
I don't use enough tools.
I mostly hack manually.
And I only sort of fast something.
If I have really big
suspicion, something is there.
And I think it's my big problem that
I don't, like, blindly fast so much.
I don't brute force pass so much.
So it's really nice for me to see, to
see you, speak with you, to see, like,
how many, how many you can actually use,
that you can have a brute force that's
running for a few days in the background.
Yeah, because you, you turn
on and for using low, because
the use of memory often Fuffy.
Uh, it's increasing.
When you have huge word release
and use the command minus E
because you have more extensions.
And I think, but probably
fluffy, uh, added to the memory.
And you were deletion with your extension.
So this is the real, it's your memory.
So I try to use, I try to
use not a lot of, Yeah.
And, uh, when you, you can test that when
you have a lot of instance of running,
you can, you didn't use a lot of memory.
So yeah, it's, it's a really good tool.
Yeah, do you do you run it from
your local computer or from a cloud?
in the past I have a history by and I
use that for for for that, but Today now
because in the past I have my my homie
address blocking on Uh, Akamai, I think.
An example.
Yeah, I was capable.
I wasn't able to open TikTok.
Because TikTok uses Akamai and I was able
to see TikTok on some other web page.
I need to call the provider
to change my IP address.
So, yeah.
Uh, so now I, I really like these guys.
I, I always recommend it to, to
all because they are, they have the
dedicated servers with a cheap price.
Yeah.
Can you send me the link as well?
So, uh, I really like these guys.
Um, let me send it to you.
It's not only Amsterdam, but
it's not only Amsterdam servers.
But other servers are, are good.
So an example I have, I
have my server running.
The, my SCO has, uh, I
think it's 64 memory honey.
It's, it's really cheap for the
price and, and the config I have.
So I have a lot of memory.
Memory.
And for a cheap price, maybe
20, $30, yes, for that.
Good, nice and unlimited,
unlimited traffic key and
one, one gigabyte connection.
So, yeah.
Yeah,
it's really good.
So I really like it.
These guys, they are really
cheapy with good servers.
Yeah.
Okay.
So you have your, you have your
automation, you have your tools.
So what bugs do you find most commonly?
Probably,
I find a lot of bugs, but
probably Uh, a lot of improper
access control bugs access.
Yes, when I have the opportunity, because
when you have access to scope with
legacy scope and scope without F what?
Yeah, probably sickle injection has has.
I remember to see a lot
of sickle injection.
Yeah, still today.
Yes, still today.
A lot of sickle injection.
SQL injection on accurate one.
So a lot of problems with all,
with, by, with WAF two, I was able
to bypass some WAFs and some cases.
I remember to see one case, it
was really, really strange because
these guys use a different.
Type of database.
There is no home SQL map and this
database, it's used, it's IBM mainframe.
So what's, what's, yeah,
what's really insane.
Yeah.
What's really insane in SQL
map was not working there.
I was needed to write custom Python script
to, uh, make that blind assumptions.
And with this blind, blind question, blind
questions that to the database, I was
capable to get the database with a name.
Okay.
Nice.
So, yeah.
It's, it's awesome.
Uh, you need to, uh, probably spend
time is the thing with, with bug bounty.
You need to spend a lot of time and
have, and be patient with the fuzzing,
for example, because the fuzzing it's
running days, a few days, because you,
you, you can't, uh, turn off the rate
limits, but probably this will, uh,
generate problems with the customers
and probably the server will be down.
So low fuzzing, fuzzing with a low.
Uh, requests, fuzzing a lot, different
hosts and, and be patient and
have, uh, have, uh, go constancy.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Consistency.
So have constancy every day when you
have free time, do it at probably
you will be get good results.
Yeah.
How do you, but because you said
broken access control, which.
I think of access control as the bug
which is quite hard to, like, fuzz.
It is more, at least in my
head, like a manual testing.
So how do you, do you?
I
really like to use authorize.
Okay.
When, when, because I'm doing fuzzing.
Uh, and, uh, you say about fuzzing
and broken access control, right?
Yeah.
Uh, I do fuzzing to get more paths
and more applications and when when
I get access to more applications
because the application is probably
not visible to all the other people,
you have a sex to older logging
systems and older systems and there.
In this application, you are capable
to find a lot of improper sess control.
Yes, basically just manually for them.
Yeah, yeah.
Because an example you have, you have
this domain, the path and in the path,
this strange path, you have access,
you have assistant with the logging.
But if you fuzz in again, you have.
Access to other path of the
application didn't, uh, other paths.
And you can find a lot of
broken access control there.
XSS, SQL injections.
So yeah, you need to spend
time for doing fuzzing.
So how, how would you
describe your normal day?
How much time do you spend running
tools versus manual hacking?
Uh, because running tools is so fast.
I only.
I only see the endpoint, get, get,
uh, the URL or send it to you or get
the endpoint sent, create the command
and, uh, use the command on cloud and
wait and spend time testing the app.
Because I was testing
what I can see on the app.
An example, I was testing the app and I
saw a lot of functions, a lot of, uh, a
lot of possibilities in this application.
I will test everything.
Every single part of the application,
every piece of this application
to understand how this work is and
what, what I can see and the fuzzy,
it's running to, it's running and I
was looking in the fuzzy and maybe
there is some, some interest in here.
I do fuzzy in API too, because
sometimes you are capable to get
swagger's and other important things
with if you fuzzy and get a swagger.
Swagger, you can't stop because
you have all the API endpoints.
So, yeah, I do a lot of fuzzing.
Yeah, so Justin, how do you
send requests directly from
Bairp to your cloud instance?
Yeah, this case I need to work
in And way to, I was thinking to
create a Python script to send
the request directly to my cloud.
But today I copied the URL, an
example, generate a first comment
and, and, and put in my cloud.
I use the screen to, I don't know
if you know the screen software.
No, it's a software on, on Linux and you
can, uh, there is a lot of servers here.
So I use this screen a lot.
Let me
see.
Is it like backgrounding
terminal or something like this?
Uh, sorry?
Putting one terminal in the background
and the other in the foreground?
Yeah.
Oh, there's a lot of fuzzing right here.
Yeah, I see.
Yeah, so with the screen, I was
capable to enable a new screen.
And here I fluffy.
After that, I Press this
and a new screen is running.
So I do that.
It's a manual working, but I was, I was
working to automate that with Python 72.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, that's cool.
Yeah, that's nice.
So much, so much things I would
like to do.
Yeah, I really like it.
There is, there is other.
Uh, tools like no hub.
I think, uh, no hobby.
That's the way I use usually no hub.
I didn't like the hub because it's
making running in background and
you can see the screen running.
I think, Oh, I don't know how to
put it to a file.
So you have to like the tail dash
file.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that's that's what I
use when I use something.
So maybe he screen works well to
me because An example, nohub, it's
running and you can stop, you only
stop nohub if you use ps and kill the
task, but in screen you can access the
screen and for if it's running I can
press enter and for if it is pause.
Yeah, that's nice.
I should probably switch.
Yeah.
So.
So it's more advanced version basically.
Yeah.
So I really like how to use the screen to
generate my all terminals on the server.
Yeah.
How about, um, cause XSS it's.
Also that much problematic that it's,
I think, harder to detect with a tool
because yeah, you can just look at the
response, but the only like proper,
proper way to detect something is to
have like a tool with a headless Chrome.
And this is heavy.
So do you use headless Chrome or
do you just use some kind of For
Doom XSS are you talking about, right?
For XSS.
Yeah.
I really like this guy.
Okay.
But always So Reflector extension.
Reflector is really good.
But always I'm looking flow, because flow
has this, this thing here reflecting.
Yeah.
And this you can see the parameters
are reflected in the page.
So with that, um, probably
there's some good things here.
But every time Reflector, it's working
in the scope and send request and I'm
looking that and look at the issues.
He, uh, the issues have vector
created and for doing XSS.
I really look, I really like
uses, uh, their birth browser.
I, I, I, I really, I didn't use burp
browser a lot because sometimes he's
browsing these browsers, some problematic,
I think, but I really like doing Vader.
So it's really, really awesome
to do XSS because I, I grabbed
this canary, DC canary, canary.
Yeah, put in the URL
and look and do invader.
If you're doing very good alert, Oh,
probably there is a DOOM XSS here, but
I really like to look at the JS and look
if I have some possibilities in, in the
JS to, to get, to get some DOOM XSS.
Yeah.
So I use Reflector.
I do a lot of fuzzy parameters, use
the sends to you, or I have these
extensions and sends to you, sends to you.
I select my, my.
My programs here, XO,
XH, XLMAP, SeriousForce.
So,
yeah.
I also saw you have a repository on
GitHub with TamperMonkey scripts.
Do you still use it a lot these days?
That repo wasn't so too
fresh, I have to say.
So, yeah, I really like to use
TamperMonkey in the past, but
it's because I didn't know about,
I didn't know about the DevOps
tool and how this work on Chrome.
So now you just use overriding of tools.
I didn't use a lot.
Today, but yes, the, the, the
scripts are really, the temporary
multiscripts are good because you
can change the app in the runtime.
And with that, maybe you can assess
other page of the application.
So I really like that.
But now using the develop tools
in Chrome, it's more, it's better.
Yeah.
Uh,
so a lot, another thing I really like
had to do it's, uh, because, uh, When
I was, when I, uh, when, uh, when,
uh, when I, I started doing, doing
hockey and, and some things, I really
like to see how these PHP apps, uh,
works and, and how the PHP apps work.
And it's really fun when, an example,
when I have a local file inclusion
with PHP apps, because with that,
you can find the source code of the
app and you can look, oh, Probably
here there is a way to get remote
code execution or upload a php file.
So our deserialization on php.
So it's it's really, I
really like it called review.
But what I do sometimes in some
scope, some scopes is an example.
I have.
This program with a large scope,
I find some apps of this program.
I search the, these paths of these
apps using URL scan, because there
you can search only for the paths
and you, the path, and you can find
other applications with the same path.
So.
Pro.
Probably this application is, uh, it's,
uh, it's not, it's hosted by this client,
but the code is not for these clients.
And sometimes you are capable to
get the source code on the internet
and he was capable to reveal the
source called the source code.
So it's, I really do that a lot.
And it's really good.
Yeah,
yeah, it's nice.
I dunno if it was you the other day
here telling me about it or somebody
else, but yeah, I didn't use it.
And the second time
somebody mentions it here.
.
Yeah.
Uh uh.
I really like, I really like how
do that, because sometimes you,
you are fine for zero days, but
not in the really purple software.
You are looking in that software.
You use it by some company.
Yeah.
That's nice.
Okay.
We'll now talk a little bit about LEDs.
Did you attended, you said, you
said you attended four LEDs in the
past, I think five, five times.
Yeah, I remember LAGs from
Amazon, AWS, PayPal, Zoom.
So I think probably the life hack
events, the life hack events are
really hard because you have a
lot of good hackers together.
Uh, testing the same scope.
So there is a lot of dupes, but for me,
probably life hack events are best because
I have some friends together with me, so
I have F6X, Amstrad, I see Amstrad, but.
A M S D A, so Manuel, T, Herrera,
Caio, uh, so Amir, so these guys
together with me, we working
together, we can do a lot of things.
I, I, that, that report, uh,
with the remote coding execution,
that scenario, it was together.
A lot of guys working
together to get that.
So
do you work as one big
group with so many people?
Yeah.
When, when, uh.
When, uh, the Brazilians guys are,
the Brazilians guys are together,
we work together, and I'll, I'll
agree with share the bounty.
So, yeah.
So it's, it's report like a six way split.
Yeah, sometimes six, five, five splits.
So, yeah, I'm okay because, uh, in
the most part of the case, we are, We
earn a lot of money and we stay okay.
I remember an example for me, an
example for me, 20, 000 is a lot of
money, but together, uh, together,
I remember all the guys made, uh, a
hundred, a hundred thousand dollars.
So five guys made a hundred
thousand dollars in the heaven.
So.
Yeah, it's, it's, for me, it's good,
probably because probably if I stay alone,
I will be not perform like that to that.
So for me, work together in life
hack events, it's really important.
I think you're the biggest team because
I think there were some teams in
the past, but these days I feel like
most people were, if there are teams,
there are teams of two, maybe three.
I'm not aware of any other group
that's like sticks with so many people.
Yeah.
Cool.
Yeah, so this case was five, last
year was three, me, F6X, and Amzda,
because we only, only we are invited.
So yeah, when, when, when the, all
the guys are invited, we do together.
When not, it's okay.
We do with the guys we have.
Um, I probably the Brazilian guys
like work together and I really like
it because are really skilled at
guys because they are guys with a
really good skills and probably we
complement we complement all together.
So yeah, that's a nice strategy.
Yeah.
Did you ever
have problems
with managing such a big team?
No.
I didn't remember to have
problems, only, only good bautis.
So the guys are really,
are really nice to do.
A lot of, they, they are
really friend, friendly.
Do you
change your hacking methodology a little
bit when working in the team or is it
exactly the same as when working alone?
So when we are, we are working
in the team, probably I do a lot
of fuzzing and recon and get all.
Uh, good information about the scope and
send to the team to we work together.
So, uh, I really like at working
at some good information.
Good, good information about the scope.
Uh, an example, find some
legacy application on some,
some good applications to test.
An example, probably this
application I find here is good.
Maybe you can spend time here
of fuzzing here and that's here.
So, yeah, I remember to.
I remember to do that with some
guys in the past and we find a
lot of zero days and applications
sent to, to lifehack haven.
So I remember, I remember to send and,
and, and vulnerability with a hater, uh,
maybe it's, it's missing, maybe, uh, Uh,
maybe, uh, the, the submission will close.
The submission will close in 30 minutes.
I think we found some
good vulnerability link.
A lot of PII we sent and the team
paid, I think the team paid 50, 000.
It was, it was really awesome.
It was really awesome.
So, yeah, it's really good work
with these guys and work together.
We really, we really
find good, good veneer
updates together.
Yeah.
Do you physically go to the same location
to hack together or is it mostly online?
So,
uh, when you, when you are Uh, because
lifehack haven't had two steps.
The first step is, uh, before
the, the, the presence here.
And after, after the ritual,
you have these guys together.
So sometimes we work together in
a discord cow and hacking, but
there is Async, uh, moments when
you send, Oh, there is some good.
We created telegram groups to talk about
that.
But for the virtual face, you did
not try to, I don't know, rent the
hacker house or something like this.
Yeah,
there is a problem because
we work far in Brazil.
It's really huge.
So I work in the north.
An example, I work in the north.
I stay in the north of Brazil.
F6X, uh, in this, in the south of Brazil.
But now in the, in the.
Northeast of Brazil.
So all are from a different
place.
Yeah.
I saw a few maps of Brazil
that really show the scale.
For example, the most Northern part
is closer to any other country in
North and South America than the
Southern part, the part, most Southern
part of Brazil or the other one.
The most eastern part of Brazil is closer
to the other side of the ocean than to the
uh, western, most western part of Brazil.
It's huge.
Yeah.
So imagine, uh, uh, from even the north of
Brazil, really near to the top of Brazil.
And we didn't have direct
flights from there.
So I need to go to the south.
And after that, go.
In example, we are going to Atlanta,
so I need to go down to Sao Paulo
and after that go to Atlanta.
Yeah.
I spent, I've been maybe, uh,
my city to Sao Paulo, I spent
four, five hours in plane.
And after that, 90 hours go to Atlanta.
Yeah.
Which of the four or five life hacking
events, which one was the best?
Um, um, I really liked the, um, the life
hacking event with, with the five guys,
because it was really, really good.
Um, the last year was really, really
good because I saw a lot of good
vulnerabilities with Manu, with Amazon.
Sorry, with Amish.
nf6x, we are capable to send good
vulnerabilities, but I really like the
last year of, last, I think it's 2023.
Yeah, 2023, because it was
five guys together and some
good bugs are sending together.
We sent a lot of bugs,
that's like hacking events.
So it was really, really good.
So I really like these two years.
Yeah.
Probably the first live
hacking event I was.
was, are not, are not my best performance.
See, so together with these guys, I
really increased my, my performance.
Nice.
Uh, we'll, we'll, uh, we're
closing in on the, on the episode
is I have the flights today.
Um, what before, but before
we go, what are your plans
for the Uh, rest of the 2025,
uh, so my plans is improving my recon
automation and spend most part of my
free time doing book bounties to save,
um, a lot of money and be in my house.
This is what I'm doing.
I'm, I'm building my house
building from the ground.
Yeah.
So I bought the, I bought
the lane, I buy the lanes.
And I bought, I, I contract and,
and some company to build the house.
Yeah.
So we are, we are building
the house and contracts.
I try to draw, draw, draw the
house, think out the, this thing.
So, yeah, but it's cool because,
uh, if, if, if I think in that,
HackerOne is paid for my house.
It's true.
I wish you good luck with this.
Thank
you so much for joining me for the
podcast
today.
Thank you so much for inviting me.
I really, I'm really happy with that.
Lovely.